

GUSTAVO RODRIGUEZ SANTELIZ

gar.santeliz@gmail.com | 786-362-1021 | Miami Beach, FL 33109

Summary

I am professional with 10 years of experience in Management in different industries such as Retail and Logistic in both sides of the market, service and goods, which now I am moving toward Tech Industry with a title of Full-Stack web developer. I bring a tool's package of communication, make-decision, work based on goal and teamwork to my new role as Full Stack Developer which I highlighted skills like coding in Javascript, React, React Router, React Hooks, HTML5 and CSS3, and Bootstrap to create layouts in client-side.

Also, my GitHub account is attached for its review, and my LinkedIn profile where you will find all my certifications.

Skills

- HTML5 proficiency
- CSS3 expertise
- JavaScript
- Dashboard creation
- Design and development
- React.js

- Bootstrap
- REST API's
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Firebase
- Interface design and implementation
- UI/UX

Experience

Freelance | Miami Beach, FL **Software Developer** 08/2021 - Current

- Managed both back-end and front-end aspects of the development process.
- Collected and defined customer requirements to produce product scopes.
- Worked with React as library to create components to improve a better readability.
- Created authentication component based on Firebase to collect data.
- Provided functionality to components with Javascript such as Map data, push data from button components and or collect data from inputs components.
- Connected components through React Router to provide a better UX.
- Created Asynchronism HTTP request to push and render data from and/or to Firebase.
- Inspected and repaired products using tools such as Excel to meet project expectations.
- Monitored QA procedures for adherence by employees, notifying personnel of non-compliance issues.
- Designed and updated test cases to complete consistent programming tests.
- Contributed to business growth by confirming customer satisfaction with service and quality.
- Documented identified defects using Excel and helped developers complete further testing and resolve issues.
- Trained end users on software and hardware functionality, best practices and protocols.
- Avoided litigation by managing confidential quality documentation to

Amazon | Opa-locka, FL Quality Assurance Specialist 10/2020 - Current ensure 100% accuracy.

 Optimized Damaged Land data accuracy by developing and revising logic and accuracy testing procedures while solving deployed device and delivery logistical issues.

Miami-Dade College | Miami, FL **Software Developer** 04/2021 - 07/2021

- Participated in code review meetings, providing input on bugs, inefficiencies and potential solutions to emergent issues.
- Designed user-friendly software interfaces to simplify overall management.
- Collaborated with product and Senior Software engineer to define and develop new product concepts.
- Developed production, test and beta websites using various software programs.
- Created new and innovative integrated content management system using React.
- Built websites managed from client-side using Firebase API to create sync and store data in realtime.
- Drafted detailed design objectives and developed architectural and system design documents.

Education and Training

Miami Dade College | Miami, FL **Full Stack Web Development** in Technology 08/2021

LinkedIn Learning | Online **Become A React Developer** in Technology Education 08/2021

University of Calgary | Calgary, Canada **English As Second Language** in Language 12/2014

Jose Antonio Paez University | Venezuela **Bachelor of Science** in Marketing 08/2010

Personal Websites

• https://linkedin.com/in/garsanteliz | https://github.com/gars150387

Languages

SpanishNative/ Bilingual

English Professional